blue-ex.com 2009-10-06

# Blue EX Couriers - benefits delivered ::: Privacy

Privacy Statement

Blue Ex respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the personal information you share with us. This statement describes how Blue Ex collects and uses your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information. 

**What is personal information?**  
Personal information means any information from which a living individual can be identified directly, or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to their physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. 

Information we collect and how we use it 

**Information you provide**  \- When you sign up for a Blue Ex account, we ask you for personal information (such as but not limited to your name, email address, phone number, client registration account number, username and password). We ask for your account number for the purpose of associating your online account with your Blue Ex account. 

**Blue Ex cookies**  \- When you visit Blue Ex.com, we send one or more cookies - parcels of text sent by our server to your web browser and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. We use cookies to improve the quality of our services. Specifically Blue Ex uses cookies to facilitate navigation through its website. The cookies help us distinguish new visitors from returning visitors and enable us to measure the electiveness of content on the website and refine that content to suit our visitor's interest. 

**We automatically collect information**  \- relating to your visit to Blue Ex.com, such as your IP address, the server into which your computer is logged on, your browser type, operating system and service provider. 

**Where we store your information**  \- Blue Ex at present has secured server in its Head Office. Blue Ex does not share your personal information with third parties for any reason whatsoever.
